girlgamesnow.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy For Girl Games Now

Girl Games Now has a privacy policy to protect all its users and visitors. Please read this page to learn how Girl Games Now (GGN) is protecting your privacy.

## 100% Privacy

We have no systems on our servers to track or store traffic information of our users and what our users are doing. We are hosting this website to bring a safe place to play free online girl games, nothing less and nothing more! Girl Games Now carefully screens all content before publishing it on its portal. Please keep reading this statement to learn more about the third party advertisers that we allow to run advertisements on our girl game portal.

## No IP address and logging

Your IP address is _not_ used to gather broad demographic information and Girl Games Now _does not_ track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). Normal log files are disabled on our server for speed and privacy reasons. The current log level of our server is 'emerg', meaning the server will only create an emergency/crash log file in the event of a complete server crash.

## Sharing Of Information

There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit girlgamesnow.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Please visit our third parties at cpmstar.com and google.com/adsense to learn more about their privacy policy and what kind of cookies they might create in your browser. Girl Games Now has no control on the privacy policy, scripts and cookies hosted by our third parties.

\- Google Adsense - [www.google.com/adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)  
\- Google Cookies Policy - [google.com/privacy_cookies.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)  
\- Adsense Privacy policy - [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
\- Cpmstar Privacy Policy - [www.cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/)

* the external hosted scripts, codes and privacy policies of our third parties are not located on our girlgamesnow.com server and may change in the future.

## What Are Cookies?

Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties.

## Opt Out

You can create special cookies that prevent the cookies from advertisers being set, please visit [networkadvertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to learn more.

## Liability

It is girlgamesnow.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, girlgamesnow.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.

girlgamesnow.com - a safe and free girl game portal
